<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<feed xml:lang="en" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:opensearch="http://a9.com/-/spec/opensearch/1.1/" xmlns:s="http://jadedpixel.com/-/spec/shopify">
  <id>https://boost.com.au/blogs/help-topics.atom</id>
  <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://boost.com.au/blogs/help-topics"/>
  <link rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" href="https://boost.com.au/blogs/help-topics/tagged/help-support.atom"/>
  <title>Boost Mobile Australia - Help Topics</title>
  <updated>2024-02-14T06:46:40+11:00</updated>
  <author>
    <name>Boost Mobile Australia</name>
  </author>
  <entry>
    <id>https://boost.com.au/blogs/help-topics/nestcalling</id>
    <published>2023-07-31T13:09:28+10:00</published>
    <updated>2023-07-31T13:10:09+10:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://boost.com.au/blogs/help-topics/nestcalling"/>
    <title>Changes to Google Voice Activated Calling</title>
    <author>
      <name>John-Scott McClure</name>
    </author>
    <content type="html">
      <![CDATA[<h1>Changes to Google Voice Activated Calling</h1>
<p><strong>From 26 September 2023, Google Voice Activated Calling will no longer be supported by Google. We'll disable it for customers from 15 September 2023.</strong></p>
<p>No Google Home or Google Nest devices will support Google Voice Activated Calling. This includes:</p>
<ul>
<li>
<strong>Speakers:</strong> Google Home, Google Nest Mini (2nd gen), Google Home Mini (1st gen), Google Home Max, Google Nest Audio, Google Nest Wifi point.</li>
<li>
<strong>Displays:</strong> Google Nest Hub and Google Nest Hub Max.</li>
</ul>
<h3><span><br>Frequently asked questions:</span></h3>
<p><strong>1. Why is the Google Voice Activated Calling feature no longer available?</strong></p>
<p><span>From time-to-time Google and their partners may add or remove features. At this time, it has been determined that Google will remove the ability to make and receive calls through all phone service partners. Therefore, Telstra is no longer able to offer this feature.</span></p>
<p><strong>2. How do I enable or disable voice-activated calling before 15 September?</strong></p>
<meta charset="UTF-8">
<p>We removed the ability to enable this feature after 29 May 2023. Anyone who signed up before then can keep using it until 15 September 2023.</p>
<p>You can disable it any time through the Call Providers settings in your Google Home app. From there, select <strong>Unlink </strong>under your Telstra mobile number.</p>
<p><strong>3. How else can I make calls from my Google Home or Nest?</strong></p>
<meta charset="UTF-8">
<p><span>Google Home and Nest devices still support the ability to make calls through services like </span><a href="https://meet.google.com/">Google Meet</a><span>.</span></p>
<p><strong>4.  Will emergency calling (000) still work once voice-activated calling is removed?</strong></p>
<p>No. You won’t be able to call 000 from your Google Home or Nest device once this feature is removed.</p>
<p><strong>5. Do I need to do anything once Google Voice Activated Calling is removed?</strong></p>
<p><span>No. Voice-activated calling will continue to work until 15 September 2023. It will then be removed automatically and links between Google and Telstra will be deleted securely.</span></p>
<p><strong>6. Will there be any notification on my Google Nest device when voice-activated calling is removed?</strong></p>
<meta charset="UTF-8">
<p><span>No. Your Google Home or Nest device won’t provide a notification when the feature is no longer active.</span></p>
<p><strong>7. Will I be charged for using Google Voice Activated Calling?</strong></p>
<p><span>No. It was free to set up and calls are made at no additional cost on the existing mobile plan of eligible Telstra mobile customers.</span></p>
<p> </p>]]>
    </content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://boost.com.au/blogs/help-topics/data-free-music-streaming-apple-music</id>
    <published>2023-07-24T14:35:07+10:00</published>
    <updated>2023-07-24T14:35:07+10:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://boost.com.au/blogs/help-topics/data-free-music-streaming-apple-music"/>
    <title>Stream Apple Music data free</title>
    <author>
      <name>John-Scott McClure</name>
    </author>
    <content type="html">
      <![CDATA[<h1>Can I stream Apple Music data free?</h1>
<p>Boost Mobile no longer offers Data Free streaming with Apple Music.</p>
<p>To find out more about what is included in our plans, click <a href="https://boost.com.au/pages/prepaid-plans" target="_blank" title="Prepaid Plans" rel="noopener noreferrer">here</a>.</p>]]>
    </content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://boost.com.au/blogs/help-topics/network-speeds</id>
    <published>2023-01-13T08:33:31+11:00</published>
    <updated>2023-12-06T15:22:47+11:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://boost.com.au/blogs/help-topics/network-speeds"/>
    <title>5G Plans and Download Speeds</title>
    <author>
      <name>Dhani Miles</name>
    </author>
    <content type="html">
      <![CDATA[<h1>5G Enabled Plans and Download Speeds</h1>
<h2>5G network access included</h2>
<p>5G network access is now available as standard on all of our plans and download speeds are capped on our 4G and 5G networks as follows:</p>
<table width="100%">
<tbody>
<tr>
<td style="width: 117.703px;"><strong style="background-color: #ffffff;">Recharge</strong></td>
<td style="width: 153.773px;"><strong style="background-color: #ffffff;">Expiry Period</strong></td>
<td style="width: 258.023px;"><strong style="background-color: #ffffff;">Download speed up to</strong></td>
</tr>
<tr>
<td style="width: 117.703px;"><span style="background-color: #ffffff;">$5-$15</span></td>
<td style="width: 153.773px;"><span style="background-color: #ffffff;">7 days</span></td>
<td style="width: 258.023px;"><span style="background-color: #ffffff;">150Mps</span></td>
</tr>
<tr>
<td style="width: 117.703px;"><span style="background-color: #ffffff;">$22-$45</span></td>
<td style="width: 153.773px;"><span style="background-color: #ffffff;">28 days</span></td>
<td style="width: 258.023px;"><span style="background-color: #ffffff;">150Mps</span></td>
</tr>
<tr>
<td style="width: 117.703px;"><span style="background-color: #ffffff;">$55</span></td>
<td style="width: 153.773px;"><span style="background-color: #ffffff;">28 days</span></td>
<td style="width: 258.023px;"><span style="background-color: #ffffff;">250Mps</span></td>
</tr>
<tr>
<td style="width: 117.703px;"><span style="background-color: #ffffff;">$70</span></td>
<td style="width: 153.773px;"><span style="background-color: #ffffff;">28 days</span></td>
<td style="width: 258.023px;"><span style="background-color: #ffffff;">Uncapped</span></td>
</tr>
<tr>
<td style="width: 117.703px;"><span style="background-color: #ffffff;">$230-$365</span></td>
<td style="width: 153.773px;"><span style="background-color: #ffffff;">12 months</span></td>
<td style="width: 258.023px;"><span style="background-color: #ffffff;">150Mps</span></td>
</tr>
</tbody>
</table>
<p> </p>
<h2>Download Speed FAQs</h2>
<p><strong>What does the capped download speed mean for me?</strong></p>
<p>As all speed cap options are great for video streaming, browsing, social media and hot-spotting a single device you should be able to continue doing what you usually do, and enjoy the same or similar mobile experience you do today. If you need to hot-spot multiple devices, or regularly transfer large files, you may benefit from uncapped download speeds. Your capped download speed is the maximum potential download speed for data included in your recharge. Typical speeds may often be slower and will vary due to factors such as location, distance from the base station, local conditions, concurrent users, hardware and software configuration and download/upload destination. 5G is rolling out in selected areas and available with a compatible device. <a href="/coverage">Check 5G coverage in your area.</a></p>
<p> </p>
<p><strong>How do I test what speeds I’m getting on 5G?</strong></p>
<p><a href="https://www.speedtest.net/apps">Test your mobile connection and speed performance. </a>Your data allowance will not be impacted by this test. Please make sure Wi-Fi is turned off when testing. To access 5G, you’ll need a 5G compatible device in a 5G coverage area.</p>
<p><strong>How do I access 5G?</strong></p>
<p>You need three things to access 5G:</p>
<ul>
<li>An active prepaid recharge</li>
<li>A 5G compatible device</li>
<li>Be in an area which has 5G coverage (check out our <a href="/coverage">coverage map</a>)</li>
</ul>
<p><strong>How do I find out which areas are covered by 5G?</strong></p>
<p>Check out our <a href="/coverage">coverage map</a>.</p>]]>
    </content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://boost.com.au/blogs/help-topics/how-to-hotspot-on-your-mobile-phone</id>
    <published>2022-06-21T11:16:32+10:00</published>
    <updated>2024-03-26T15:30:32+11:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://boost.com.au/blogs/help-topics/how-to-hotspot-on-your-mobile-phone"/>
    <title>How to Hotspot on Your Mobile</title>
    <author>
      <name>Dhani Miles</name>
    </author>
    <content type="html">
      <![CDATA[<h1>How to Hotspot on Your Mobile Phone</h1>
<p>Hotspotting is a feature available on most mobile devices that allows people to share their wi-fi network with others nearby. It’s especially helpful for people who need to connect multiple devices to the internet on the fly.<br><br>Keep reading to learn more about how hotspotting works and how you can set a wireless hotspot up on your own smartphone.</p>
<h2>How to Set Up a Hotspot</h2>
<p>Setting up a hotspot on your mobile device is quick and easy. First, make sure that your phone’s software is updated to the latest version.</p>
<p>Depending on your phone, the step-by-step set up process may vary slightly. However, most will require you to go into your device’s “Settings” options.</p>
<h3>Set Up Hotspot on Android</h3>
<p>To set up the hotspot feature on your Android phone, navigate to “Settings”, tap on “Network &amp; Internet”, and go into “Hotspot &amp; Tethering”. From here, you can share your hotspot connection via wi-fi, USB or Bluetooth.</p>
<h3>Set Up Hotspot on iPhone IOS</h3>
<p>To set up the hotspot feature on your iPhone, simply head into “Settings” and enable “Personal Hotspot”. You will need to toggle on the “Allow Others to Join” option.</p>
<p>After enabling your hotspot, you can set up your own wi-fi password to secure your hotspot data usage and wi-fi network. By setting up a password, you can manage your mobile hotspot by picking and choosing which devices you allow to connect to your network. </p>
<p>Pro tip: Make sure you also keep an eye on your phone plan’s data allowance so that you don’t run out of your high speed data by hotspotting to more devices. </p>
<h2>How to Connect to a Hotspot</h2>
<p>Connecting to a hotspot is similar to connecting to any other wi-fi network. The process is generally the same across all devices and hotspot networks.</p>
<p>Below are the few steps you need to take to connect to a hotspot:</p>
<ol>
<li>Tap on the wireless icon on your device</li>
<li>Enter the security key or wi-fi password as directed (you will need to find out the password from the hotspot owner)</li>
<li>Choose the network type to determine how discoverable your device will be to other devices (e.g. private or public) and allow access permission</li>
</ol>
<p>Follow the steps above and you’ll be able to connect to all hotspot wi-fi networks on any device.</p>
<h2>How do Hotspots Work?</h2>
<p>Hotspots need a connection to a cellular network to work. Service providers such as Boost Mobile give your phone access to internet, which you can then hotspot to other devices such as tablets and laptops.</p>
<p>Hotspots usually provide a wi-fi connection via wireless technology. Mobile data speeds usually average around 50Mbps, although some may reach up to 1,000 Mbps. If your phone plan uses 4G wireless technology, you may experience lower speeds when sharing internet access with your hotspot.</p>
<p>Due to being conveniently accessible, you can set up a personal hotspot on your phone to share with people nearby or your other wi-fi enabled devices. </p>
<h2>Hotspot FAQs</h2>
<h3>What is a hotspot?</h3>
<p>A hotspot is a physical place where users can wirelessly connect to a local network to access the internet. They are also known as “wi-fi hotspots” and “wi-fi connections”. Just like a regular wi-fi network from any internet service provider, all types of devices can connect to and use a hotspot, from phones to tablets to laptops and computers. </p>
<p>Gone are the days of using a USB cable to connect to the internet - hotspots are a much easier and more convenient way to stay connected to the internet. A hotspot can be private or public, depending on the service provider. Public hotspots are normally available at hotels, coffee shops, airports and shopping centres. Some may require a password for exclusive access to the wi-fi hotspot.</p>
<p>On top of regular hotspots are mobile hotspots. As the name implies, these hotspots can move around depending on the location of the dedicated hotspot devices. You can use your mobile phone as a hotspot to share your cellular network and internet connection with others. This is a process known as “tethering”.</p>
<h3>Do hotspots use more data?</h3>
<p>Hotspotting from your phone will naturally use more data as another device will be connected to your network. Devices of the same type such as another smartphone will use similar levels of data, while larger devices such as laptops may use more data.</p>
<h3>How to use iPhone as hotspot?</h3>
<p>You can use an iPhone as a hotspot by simply going into your “Settings”, tapping “Personal Hotspot” and toggling the “Allow Others to Join” option. You can set a wi-fi password as well to make your hotspot connection more secure.</p>
<h3>Does hotspot drain battery?</h3>
<p>Using your phone as a mobile hotspot will drain battery on your device. This is because your phone is using more power to stay connected to a wi-fi network while sharing it with others.</p>
<h3>How secure is a mobile hotspot?</h3>
<p>Most phones offering mobile hotspot features have some form of default security such as WPA-PSK encryption, an SSID and network key. However, to add a greater level of security, it is recommended that you set a wi-fi password on your hotspot so that only devices you approve can access your network.</p>
<h3>Is there 5G hotspot?</h3>
<p>Many cellular data providers now allow hotspots to work over a 5G network. This allows connections to be quicker and smartphones to access faster internet speeds via hotspots.</p>]]>
    </content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://boost.com.au/blogs/help-topics/where-to-go-for-help-support</id>
    <published>2021-12-03T17:19:11+11:00</published>
    <updated>2021-12-03T17:20:45+11:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://boost.com.au/blogs/help-topics/where-to-go-for-help-support"/>
    <title>Where to go for Help &amp; Support</title>
    <author>
      <name>Emily Peake</name>
    </author>
    <content type="html">
      <![CDATA[<h1>Where to go for Help &amp; Support</h1>
<p>If you have a question, chances are someone else has a similar one.</p>
<p>Check out our <a href="https://boost.com.au/pages/help-topics" title="Boost FAQs">FAQs</a> , <a href="https://refurbished.boost.com.au/pages/frequently-asked-questions" title="Refurbished FAQs">Refurbished FAQs</a>, or our <a href="https://boost.com.au/pages/get-help" title="Help &amp; Support Blog">Help &amp; Support articles.</a></p>
<p>Or you can get it touch using of the following methods:</p>
<ul>
<li>Chat to us on <a href="https://www.facebook.com/boostaus" target="_blank" title="Boost Mobile Australia Facebook" rel="noopener noreferrer">Facebook</a> - available 24/7</li>
<li>Message Us - available 7am-11pm AEST, 7 days</li>
<li>Call us on 1800 100 933 - available 8am-8pm AEST, 7days </li>
</ul>
<p> </p>]]>
    </content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://boost.com.au/blogs/help-topics/how-to-use-google-pay</id>
    <published>2021-12-03T17:04:47+11:00</published>
    <updated>2023-10-25T10:32:05+11:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://boost.com.au/blogs/help-topics/how-to-use-google-pay"/>
    <title>How to use Google Pay - Help and Support - Boost Mobile</title>
    <author>
      <name>Emily Peake</name>
    </author>
    <content type="html">
      <![CDATA[<h1>How to use Google Pay</h1>
<p>Google Pay is a mobile payments app that allows you to store your credit &amp; debit cards, shopping (aka loyalty) cards all in a simple and easy location on your supported Android phone.<br> <br><strong>So can I use Google Pay?</strong><br><strong> </strong><br>There are a few things to check to ensure you are ready for Google Pay</p>
<ul>
<li>Is your bank / financial provider supporting Google Pay? Check out the list of available providers <a href="https://support.google.com/pay/answer/7351634" target="_blank" title="Google Pay Providers" rel="noopener noreferrer">here</a>
</li>
<li>Make sure your phone is running at least Android Kit Kat 4.4 or higher</li>
<li>You need to download the Google Pay app to your Android device. You can find that<span> </span><a href="https://play.google.com/store/apps/details?id=com.google.android.apps.walletnfcrel" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer" title="Google Pay App">here</a>.</li>
<li>Make sure you have a compatible phone. Most flagship Android phones from the last two years can use Google Pay, however if you were not sure, open the Google Pay app and check its compatibility. If your device is not compatible you will receive one of the following error messages - "Google Pay can’t be used”, “Google is unable to verify your device”, “You can no longer use Google Pay on this phone”.</li>
</ul>
<p><strong>How do I set up Google Pay?</strong></p>
<p>Simply head over to the Google Pay app and click the blue ‘get started’ button! This will guide you through the process to add your specific card and even give you the option to scan your card using your device’s camera so you don’t need to type in those numbers! (You can also type your numbers in manually if this is your thing)</p>
<p>Once done, you will go through a security verification process (just to make sure it’s you) then voila, you’re done!<br> <br><strong>Is Google Pay safe?</strong></p>
<p>Google Pay has a multi-layered secured system to ensure your transactions are safe. When you are making a payment in store, Google Pay is not sharing the actual card information. The merchant is instead receiving a unique and encrypted number to complete the transaction.</p>
<p>Even if you lose your phone, you can use the ‘Find my phone’ feature and shut down access to Google Pay.<br> <br><strong>So where can I use Google Pay?</strong></p>
<p>Anywhere that has the Google Pay logo. This can often be found on the EFTPOS pad and / or register where you are making the purchase. Simply when prompted, hold your phone up to the EFTPOS pad and your phone will confirm payment has been made.</p>]]>
    </content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://boost.com.au/blogs/help-topics/how-to-use-apple-pay</id>
    <published>2021-12-03T16:58:55+11:00</published>
    <updated>2023-10-25T10:31:42+11:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://boost.com.au/blogs/help-topics/how-to-use-apple-pay"/>
    <title>How to use Apple Pay - Help and Support - Boost Mobile</title>
    <author>
      <name>Emily Peake</name>
    </author>
    <content type="html">
      <![CDATA[<h1>How to use Apple Pay?</h1>
<p>Apple pay is making it easier to make purchases from your iPhone or Apple Watch. Make everyday purchases in stores, in-apps and on participating websites in ways simpler and safer than using your actual card.<br><br><strong>So can I use Apple Pay?</strong></p>
<p>There are a few things to check to ensure you are ready for Apple Pay.</p>
<ul>
<li>Is your bank / financial provider supporting Apple Pay? Check out the list of available providers <a href="https://support.apple.com/en-au/HT206638" title="Apple Pay Providers">here</a>
</li>
<li>Is your Apple Device compatible? Apple Pay works on iPhone 6, 6 Plus, iPhone 6S, 6S Plus, 7, 7 Plus, 8, 8 Plus, iPhone X, iPhone SE, iPad Air 2, iPad Pro and the Apple Watch.</li>
<li>You have the latest version of iOS on your device. Simply head to Settings &gt; General &gt; Software Update</li>
</ul>
<p> </p>
<p><strong>How do I set up Apple Pay?</strong></p>
<p>Does your device meet the above? Great! Simply head to the ‘Wallet’ app on your device and select ‘Add Credit or Debit Card’ and follow the prompts. This will go through a process to ensure everything is compatible for use.<br><br><strong>Is Apple Pay Safe?</strong></p>
<p>Apple Pay utilises a number which is specific to your device and a transaction number that is unique to this type of transaction. Your card number is not stored on your device nor are they shared with merchants using Apple Pay. Plus, it’s always handy to have either a pin or Face ID enabled on your device for added protection.<br><br><strong>Where can I use Apple Pay?</strong></p>
<p>Simply look for the Apple Pay logo. Generally these can be found at the checkout or on the EFTPOS pad.</p>]]>
    </content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://boost.com.au/blogs/help-topics/boost-id</id>
    <published>2021-12-03T15:49:06+11:00</published>
    <updated>2023-11-16T11:14:39+11:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://boost.com.au/blogs/help-topics/boost-id"/>
    <title>Username and Password - Help and Support - Boost Mobile</title>
    <author>
      <name>Emily Peake</name>
    </author>
    <content type="html">
      <![CDATA[<h1><span data-mce-fragment="1">What is my username and password?</span></h1>
<p><strong><span data-mce-fragment="1">Formerly known as a Boost ID, your Boost username and password are used to access and manage your Boost service.</span></strong></p>
<p>Your username is the email address you used to activate your Boost service with us. It enables you to securely access and manage specific features in the app, such as:<br data-mce-fragment="1"><br>- Set up and manage auto recharge<br data-mce-fragment="1">- Save and manage your credit / debit card details<br data-mce-fragment="1">- Manage multiple services<br data-mce-fragment="1">- View your usage history<br data-mce-fragment="1">- View your recharge history</p>
<h3>How to recover username in the My Boost Mobile app:</h3>
<p>1. Open the My Boost Mobile app and tap the black "Sign in" button at the bottom of the screen.<br>2. Tap "Recover username" under the username text field.<br>3. Choose how you want to recover the username by selecting email address or Boost mobile number.<br>4. Tap the black "Let's get started" button. <br>5. Now enter your email address. <br>6. You should receive an email from us shortly with you username. If you can't find it in your inbox, please check your junk mail.<br>7. Tap the sign in button.</p>
<h3>How do I reset my password?</h3>
<p>When prompted, enter your username in the box provided, and click Send. <br data-mce-fragment="1"><br data-mce-fragment="1">An email will be sent with a link to reset your password. Simply click on the link and follow the prompts.<br data-mce-fragment="1"><br>Now you're good to go! You can sign into the My Boost Mobile app and access the additional features.<br data-mce-fragment="1"><br></p>
<ol></ol>]]>
    </content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://boost.com.au/blogs/help-topics/wifi-calling</id>
    <published>2021-12-03T15:30:48+11:00</published>
    <updated>2023-10-25T10:38:11+11:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://boost.com.au/blogs/help-topics/wifi-calling"/>
    <title>Wi-Fi Calling - Help and Support - Boost Mobile</title>
    <author>
      <name>Emily Peake</name>
    </author>
    <content type="html">
      <![CDATA[<h1>Does Boost support Wi-Fi Calling?</h1>
<p>Wi-Fi calling enables you to make calls using a fixed Wi-Fi connection from your compatible Boost phone when you can’t connect to the mobile network. Your phone simply uses your Wi-Fi network instead of the mobile network, so you can make and receive calls as you would normally.</p>
<p> </p>
<p><strong>To use Wi-Fi calling, you need to:</strong></p>
<ul>
<li>Have a Wi-Fi calling compatible smartphone or tablet</li>
<li>Have 4G voice calls enabled</li>
<li>Have up-to-date software</li>
<li>Turn on Wi-Fi calling</li>
</ul>
<p> </p>
<p><strong><span class="heading-16">How do I turn on Wi-Fi calling?</span></strong></p>
<p>For iPhone:</p>
<ol>
<li>Go to <strong>Settings</strong>
</li>
<li>Select <strong>Mobile</strong>
</li>
<li>Turn on <strong>Wi-Fi calling</strong>
</li>
</ol>
<p> </p>
<p>For Android devices:</p>
<ol>
<li>Go to your phone's calling app</li>
<li>Select <strong>More </strong>or the three dots in the top right corner</li>
<li>Select <strong>Settings</strong>
</li>
<li>Turn on <strong>Wi-Fi Calling</strong>
</li>
</ol>]]>
    </content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://boost.com.au/blogs/help-topics/included-calls</id>
    <published>2021-12-03T13:48:03+11:00</published>
    <updated>2023-10-25T10:33:08+11:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://boost.com.au/blogs/help-topics/included-calls"/>
    <title>Included Calls - Help and Support - Boost Mobile</title>
    <author>
      <name>Emily Peake</name>
    </author>
    <content type="html">
      <![CDATA[<h1>What types of calls are included in Boost plans?</h1>
<p>All our plans include unlimited calls and text to standard national numbers, which means you can call regular landline and mobile numbers as much as you like. This also includes most 1800, 1300 or 13 numbers.</p>
<p>It e<span>xcludes calls and texts to international numbers, satellite and premium numbers (eg. 19xx numbers), operator assisted calls (most 12xx numbers) and all use overseas.</span></p>
<p>Some of our plans also include standard calls to international numbers.</p>
<p>For more information about our current plan inclusions, click <a href="https://boost.com.au/pages/prepaid-plans" title="Prepaid Plans">here</a>.</p>]]>
    </content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://boost.com.au/blogs/help-topics/data-sharing</id>
    <published>2021-12-03T13:40:43+11:00</published>
    <updated>2023-10-25T10:30:22+11:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://boost.com.au/blogs/help-topics/data-sharing"/>
    <title>Data Sharing - Help and Support - Boost Mobile</title>
    <author>
      <name>Emily Peake</name>
    </author>
    <content type="html">
      <![CDATA[<h1>Does Boost offer data sharing?</h1>
<p>No, Boost doesn't offer data sharing between your service and and another Boost service.</p>]]>
    </content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://boost.com.au/blogs/help-topics/smart-watch</id>
    <published>2021-12-03T13:26:31+11:00</published>
    <updated>2023-10-25T10:37:02+11:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://boost.com.au/blogs/help-topics/smart-watch"/>
    <title>Smart watch compatibility - Help and Support - Boost Mobile</title>
    <author>
      <name>Emily Peake</name>
    </author>
    <content type="html">
      <![CDATA[<h1>Can I use my Smart watch with Boost?</h1>
<p>Boost doesn't currently support the use of cellular Smartwatches with your existing number, including Apple watches and Samsung Galaxy watches.</p>
<p><span>However we are working on it as we know its something our customers are interested in.</span></p>]]>
    </content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://boost.com.au/blogs/help-topics/does-boost-have-esim-capability</id>
    <published>2021-12-03T13:19:57+11:00</published>
    <updated>2024-03-12T14:43:25+11:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://boost.com.au/blogs/help-topics/does-boost-have-esim-capability"/>
    <title>Does Boost have eSIM capability</title>
    <author>
      <name>Emily Peake</name>
    </author>
    <content type="html">
      <![CDATA[<h1>Does Boost Mobile have eSIM capability?</h1>
<p>We sure do! And the best news... All of our plans are available on eSIM.</p>
<p>All you have to do to sign up for your eSIM service is download the My Boost Mobile app and select “Buy a prepaid plan on eSIM” and follow the prompts. It’s pretty straightforward though, tbh.</p>
<p><a href="https://boost.com.au/pages/esim" title="eSIM Boost Mobile">More info on Boost Mobile eSIM.</a></p>]]>
    </content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://boost.com.au/blogs/help-topics/change-account-ownership</id>
    <published>2021-12-01T15:35:06+11:00</published>
    <updated>2023-10-25T10:28:46+11:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://boost.com.au/blogs/help-topics/change-account-ownership"/>
    <title>Change account ownership - Help and Support - Boost Mobile</title>
    <author>
      <name>Emily Peake</name>
    </author>
    <content type="html">
      <![CDATA[<h1>How to change your account ownership</h1>
<p>To transfer your account to another person, or to update account details, please contact us. You can call 1800 100 933 or Message Us on our <a href="https://boost.com.au/pages/get-help" target="_blank" title="Help" rel="noopener noreferrer">help</a> page.</p>]]>
    </content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://boost.com.au/blogs/help-topics/extend-your-ring-time</id>
    <published>2021-12-01T15:04:34+11:00</published>
    <updated>2023-10-25T10:30:41+11:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://boost.com.au/blogs/help-topics/extend-your-ring-time"/>
    <title>Extend your ring time - Help and Support - Boost Mobile</title>
    <author>
      <name>Emily Peake</name>
    </author>
    <content type="html">
      <![CDATA[<h1>How to extend your ring time</h1>
<p>To extend your phone's ring time, follow these simple steps:</p>
<ol>
<li>On your Boost mobile dial **61*101**(number of seconds: 15, 20, 25 or 30)#</li>
<li>Press the Call/Send button</li>
</ol>
For example, to extend your ring time to 30 seconds, you would dial **61*101**30#]]>
    </content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://boost.com.au/blogs/help-topics/manage-your-service</id>
    <published>2021-12-01T12:32:15+11:00</published>
    <updated>2024-03-26T15:37:45+11:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://boost.com.au/blogs/help-topics/manage-your-service"/>
    <title>Manage your service - Help and Support - Boost Mobile</title>
    <author>
      <name>Emily Peake</name>
    </author>
    <content type="html">
      <![CDATA[<h1>How to manage your service</h1>
<p><strong>The easiest way to manage your service is in the My Boost Mobile app and online.</strong></p>
<p>With the My Boost Mobile app you can recharge, set up auto recharge, check you balance, see your usage &amp; recharge history, get help and more. </p>
<p>My Boost Mobile is available for <a href="https://apps.apple.com/au/app/my-boost-mobile/id1536871973" title="My Boost Mobile App iOS" target="_blank">iOS</a> and <a href="https://play.google.com/store/apps/details?id=com.boost.mobile.myboost" title="My Boost Mobile app Android" target="_blank">Android</a> and is for customers on the Boost Mobile Prepaid Plan. </p>
<p>You can also recharge on our website by <a href="https://myaccount.boost.com.au/" title="sign in">signing in</a> or using our online<a href="https://boost.com.au/enternumber" title="Quick recharge"> recharge</a> option. </p>
<p> </p>]]>
    </content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://boost.com.au/blogs/help-topics/prank-or-unwanted-calls</id>
    <published>2021-12-01T12:24:03+11:00</published>
    <updated>2023-10-25T10:35:40+11:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://boost.com.au/blogs/help-topics/prank-or-unwanted-calls"/>
    <title>Spam, prank or unwanted calls - Help and Support - Boost Mobile</title>
    <author>
      <name>Emily Peake</name>
    </author>
    <content type="html">
      <![CDATA[<h1>How to stop spam, prank or unwanted calls</h1>
<p>If you are experiencing nuisance calls or messages, please contact us so we can further investigate it with you. You can either call us on 1800 100 933 or Message us by clicking "Message Us" on our <a href="https://boost.com.au/pages/get-help" target="_blank" title="Help" rel="noopener noreferrer">Help</a> page </p>
<p>If you are getting telemarking calls you can sign up for the <a href="https://www.donotcall.gov.au" target="_blank" title="Do Not Call Register" rel="noopener noreferrer">Do Not Call</a> register. You can also report unwanted calls to the Australian Communications &amp; Media Authority <a href="https://www.acma.gov.au/" target="_blank" title="ACMA" rel="noopener noreferrer">here</a>.</p>]]>
    </content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://boost.com.au/blogs/help-topics/mms-inclusions</id>
    <published>2021-12-01T11:38:22+11:00</published>
    <updated>2023-10-25T10:34:33+11:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://boost.com.au/blogs/help-topics/mms-inclusions"/>
    <title>MMS Inclusions - Help and Support - Boost Mobile</title>
    <author>
      <name>Emily Peake</name>
    </author>
    <content type="html">
      <![CDATA[<h1>Is MMS included my plan?</h1>
<p>Yes! MMS is included in all Boost Mobile plans as part of your unlimited standard national calls &amp; text inclusions. </p>
<p>If you are on a $35+ plan, then your plan also includes an allocation of standard international text (including MMS) to any destination.</p>
<p>For more information about our current plans, click <a href="https://boost.com.au/pages/prepaid-plans" target="_blank" title="Prepaid Plans" rel="noopener noreferrer">here</a>.</p>]]>
    </content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://boost.com.au/blogs/help-topics/recharge-history</id>
    <published>2021-12-01T11:30:29+11:00</published>
    <updated>2023-11-15T13:18:16+11:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://boost.com.au/blogs/help-topics/recharge-history"/>
    <title>Recharge History - Help and Support - Boost Mobile</title>
    <author>
      <name>Emily Peake</name>
    </author>
    <content type="html">
      <![CDATA[<h1><strong>How do I see my recharge history?</strong></h1>
<p> <strong>You can see your recharge history in the My Boost Mobile app.</strong></p>
<p><br>Simply open the My Boost Mobile app and sign in with your username and password. Once logged in, tap on your phone number and scroll to the bottom of your balance summary screen. There you will see "Recharge History" - tap this and you'll be able to see your recharge history including when you recharged, how much you recharged, and your payment method. <br><br>Where available you'll also be able to download a Receipt and Tax Invoice.</p>
<p>If you need<span> more information, please message us by clicking the 'Message Us' button on our </span><a href="https://boost.com.au/pages/get-help" title="Help">Help</a><span> page.</span></p>]]>
    </content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://boost.com.au/blogs/help-topics/sim-card-error</id>
    <published>2021-12-01T10:57:16+11:00</published>
    <updated>2023-10-25T10:36:38+11:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://boost.com.au/blogs/help-topics/sim-card-error"/>
    <title>SIM Card Error - Help and Support - Boost Mobile</title>
    <author>
      <name>Emily Peake</name>
    </author>
    <content type="html">
      <![CDATA[<h1>How can I fix my SIM card error?</h1>
<p><strong>There are a number of reasons that you are experiencing a SIM card error.</strong></p>
<p><strong></strong>If your SIM is not installed properly, try turning off the phone, taking the sim out and putting it back in (make sure it it seated correctly) before restarting your phone. </p>
<p>If this doesn't work, your SIM may be damaged or faulty and you'll likely need to order a replacement SIM.</p>
<p>Please contact us to further troubleshoot your error or order a replacement SIM. You can either give us a call on 125 88881 ( 8am-8pm AEST 7 days) or Message us <a href="https://boost.com.au/pages/get-help" target="_blank" title="Help" rel="noopener noreferrer">here</a>.</p>]]>
    </content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://boost.com.au/blogs/help-topics/check-for-service-disruptions</id>
    <published>2021-12-01T10:48:05+11:00</published>
    <updated>2023-10-25T10:29:32+11:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://boost.com.au/blogs/help-topics/check-for-service-disruptions"/>
    <title>Check for service disruptions - Help and Support - Boost Mobile</title>
    <author>
      <name>Emily Peake</name>
    </author>
    <content type="html">
      <![CDATA[<h1 style="text-align: left;">How to check for outages or service disruptions</h1>
<p style="text-align: left;"><span></span><span><strong>If you are unable to use your Boost Mobile to send SMS, make calls or get online, it may be due to a disruption to Boost Mobile services. These issues can range from hardware faults to outages or scheduled maintenance on the Telstra Mobile Network infrastructure.</strong></span></p>
<p style="text-align: left;">Click <a title="Service Status Tool" href="https://outages.telstra.com.au/#/mobile?pageSource=home" target="_blank">here</a> to check if there is an outage or service disruption in your area. </p>
<p style="text-align: left;">On this page you'll find updates on issues affecting our services across the country and where possible, provide an estimate restoration time so you know how long it will be until services are back up and running. </p>
<p style="text-align: left;">If there are no known issues in your area, please contact us. The easiest way to get in touch is to Message us from our <a title="Help" href="https://boost.com.au/pages/get-help">Help</a> page. </p>]]>
    </content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://boost.com.au/blogs/help-topics/extras-data-packs</id>
    <published>2021-03-18T12:35:05+11:00</published>
    <updated>2023-09-27T17:22:51+10:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://boost.com.au/blogs/help-topics/extras-data-packs"/>
    <title>Need a Little Extra Data on Your Boost Mobile Plan?</title>
    <author>
      <name>John-Scott McClure</name>
    </author>
    <content type="html">
      <![CDATA[<div class="vc_row wpb_row vc_row-fluid vc_row-o-content-top vc_row-flex wpex-vc-has-custom-column-spacing wpex-vc-column-spacing-0px">
<div class="wpb_column vc_column_container vc_col-sm-12 wpex-vc_col-has-fill">
<div class="vc_column-inner vc_custom_1582761165437">
<div class="wpb_wrapper">
<div class="wpb_text_column wpb_content_element vc_custom_1612222131751 wpex-rcss-1" data-wpex-rcss='{"font-size":{"d":"14px","tl":"14px","tp":"13px","pl":"12px","pp":"11px"}}'>
<div class="wpb_wrapper">
<h1 style="text-align: left;"><strong>Need a little Extra data?</strong></h1>
<p><strong></strong><strong>Extras are perfect for those times that you need just a bit more on top of your current recharge. You can grab one using your favourite recharge method.</strong></p>
<p>The current Boost Mobile Prepaid Plan has two Extra’s available:</p>
<ul>
<li>$5 Data Pack – includes 1GB with a 7 day expiry</li>
<li>$20 Data Pack – includes 4GB with a 28 day expiry.</li>
</ul>
<p>If you’re on Boost Anytime Ultra or Boost Anytime Plus (joined Boost between 31 October 2017 and 1 February 2021 and have not been updated to Boost Mobile Prepaid), there are two Add-Ons available.</p>
<ul>
<li>$5 Add-On – includes 1B of data and $5 credit that can be used towards data (at standard rates), calls &amp; text to satellite and premium numbers (e.g. 19xx numbers), operator assisted calls (most 12xx numbers)</li>
<li>$15 Add-On – includes 3GB of data and $15 credit that can be used towards data (at standard rates), calls &amp; text to satellite and premium numbers (e.g. 19xx numbers), operator assisted calls (most 12xx numbers) and international calls and text from Australia not included in your recharge.</li>
</ul>
<p>If you’re on UNLTD Plus (joined Boost between 12 July 2016 – 31 October 2017 and have not been updated to Boost Mobile Prepaid) you can grab a $15 Bolt-On.</p>
<p>If you’re on UNLTD (joined before 12 July 2016 and have not changed your offer) you can grab a $10 Add-On. Both include credit to use on international calls/text, data and premium services.</p>
</div>
</div>
</div>
</div>
</div>
</div>]]>
    </content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://boost.com.au/blogs/help-topics/how-long-do-i-not-have-to-recharge-before-my-number-expires</id>
    <published>2021-03-16T11:48:31+11:00</published>
    <updated>2023-10-25T10:31:26+11:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://boost.com.au/blogs/help-topics/how-long-do-i-not-have-to-recharge-before-my-number-expires"/>
    <title>Does you number expire - Help and Support - Boost Mobile</title>
    <author>
      <name>John-Scott McClure</name>
    </author>
    <content type="html">
      <![CDATA[<h1>How long before my number expires?</h1>
<p><span><strong>Your number will expire if you do not recharge your service for 6 months.</strong></span></p>]]>
    </content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://boost.com.au/blogs/help-topics/which-data-gets-used-first</id>
    <published>2021-03-16T11:47:46+11:00</published>
    <updated>2021-12-20T11:52:21+11:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://boost.com.au/blogs/help-topics/which-data-gets-used-first"/>
    <title>Boost Mobile Data: What Gets Used First</title>
    <author>
      <name>John-Scott McClure</name>
    </author>
    <content type="html">
      <![CDATA[<h1>Which data gets used first, bonus data or regular data?</h1>
<p><span>Your bonus data is used first, followed by your regular recharge data and then any rollover data.</span></p>]]>
    </content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://boost.com.au/blogs/help-topics/how-to-check-your-bonus-rollover-data</id>
    <published>2021-03-16T11:45:51+11:00</published>
    <updated>2024-03-26T15:40:04+11:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://boost.com.au/blogs/help-topics/how-to-check-your-bonus-rollover-data"/>
    <title>Check Bonus or Boost Rollover Data</title>
    <author>
      <name>John-Scott McClure</name>
    </author>
    <content type="html">
      <![CDATA[<h1>How do I check my bonus or rollover data?</h1>
<p>You can check your bonus and rollover data using the Boost app or your phone. </p>
<p><strong><span>To check bonus/rollover data u</span></strong><strong>sing the My Boost Mobile app</strong></p>
<ol>
<li>Open the app </li>
<li>Tap on your Prepaid Service</li>
<li>Tap data breakdown - your bonus data / rollover data will be displayed</li>
</ol>
<p>The My Boost Mobile app is available on<span> </span><a aria-describedby="a11y-new-window-message" href="https://play.google.com/store/apps/details?id=com.boost.mobile.myboost&amp;hl=en" target="_blank">Android</a><span> </span>and<span> </span><a aria-describedby="a11y-new-window-message" title="https://apps.apple.com/au/app/my-boost-mobile/id1536871973" href="https://apps.apple.com/au/app/my-boost-mobile/id1536871973" target="_blank">iPhone</a>.  </p>
<ol></ol>]]>
    </content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://boost.com.au/blogs/help-topics/how-to-recharge</id>
    <published>2021-03-16T11:43:00+11:00</published>
    <updated>2024-03-26T15:38:40+11:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://boost.com.au/blogs/help-topics/how-to-recharge"/>
    <title>How To Recharge With Boost Prepaid</title>
    <author>
      <name>John-Scott McClure</name>
    </author>
    <content type="html">
      <![CDATA[<h1>How do I recharge?</h1>
<h3>There are five ways to recharge with Boost.</h3>
1. On our <a href="https://boost.com.au/get-help/my-boost-mobile-app/">app</a><br data-mce-fragment="1">2. Quick recharge <a href="https://boost.com.au/">online</a><br data-mce-fragment="1">3. Sign in to our <a href="https://myaccount.boost.com.au/">website</a><br data-mce-fragment="1"><br>If you experience issues recharging, please Message us <a title="Help" href="https://boost.com.au/pages/get-help">here</a>.]]>
    </content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://boost.com.au/blogs/help-topics/bring-my-number</id>
    <published>2021-03-16T11:40:39+11:00</published>
    <updated>2021-12-20T12:05:57+11:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://boost.com.au/blogs/help-topics/bring-my-number"/>
    <title>Transfer Your Number to Boost</title>
    <author>
      <name>John-Scott McClure</name>
    </author>
    <content type="html">
      <![CDATA[<h1>How do I bring my number to Boost?</h1>
<p><strong>Transferring your number to Boost Mobile service is easy. </strong></p>
<p>Simply head to <a href="https://prepaid.activate.boost.com.au" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer"><u>activate</u></a> and choose ‘keep existing number'. You do not need to contact your previous provider. We’ll sort that out with them.</p>
<p><strong>Please keep your old SIM in your phone until you’ve completed the activation form, </strong>as you’ll be sent an SMS to verify you have access to the phone number that is being transferred.</p>
<p>Your number should be active on Boost Mobile within 4 to 24 hours after activating. If you make a request outside business hours, including Sundays and public holidays, we’ll process it on the next business day. You can still use the number with your previous provider until the switch to us is complete.</p>
<p>If your number has not moved across to Boost within 24 hours or you experience issues during the porting process, Message us <a href="https://boost.com.au/pages/get-help" title="Help">here</a></p>]]>
    </content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://boost.com.au/blogs/help-topics/activate-your-sim</id>
    <published>2021-03-16T11:39:50+11:00</published>
    <updated>2023-12-11T15:06:10+11:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://boost.com.au/blogs/help-topics/activate-your-sim"/>
    <title>Boost Mobile Activation: Activate Your SIM</title>
    <author>
      <name>John-Scott McClure</name>
    </author>
    <content type="html">
      <![CDATA[<h1>How do I activate my SIM?</h1>
<p><span><strong>You can activate your SIM using your existing number or we’ll give you a new one.</strong></span></p>
<p><strong>Before you start, you’ll need:</strong></p>
<ul>
<li>Your SIM serial number - you can find this on the back of your SIM pack</li>
<li>One valid form of ID - Australian driver’s license or learner’s permit, Medicare card, Australian passport, International passport with valid Australian visa</li>
</ul>
<p><strong>To activate your SIM</strong></p>
<p>Simply head to <a href="https://prepaid.activate.boost.com.au" target="_blank"><u>activate</u></a> and follow the steps.</p>
<p>If you wish to keep your existing number simply select “Keep existing number” during the activation process. You’ll be sent an SMS to verify you have access to the phone number that is being transferred.</p>
<p><strong>Please keep your old SIM in your phone until you’ve completed the activation form.</strong></p>
<p> </p>
<p>When you’ve completed the activation form you’ll receive an SMS and email to confirm your activation is underway.</p>
<p>Your number should be active within 4 to 24 hours after activating.  If you make a request outside business hours, including Sundays and public holidays, we’ll process it on the next business day. If you are keeping your existing number, you can still use the number with your previous provider until the switch to us is complete.</p>
<p>When your Boost SIM is active, you’ll receive an SMS or email notification letting you know that your Boost Mobile service is ready to use. Learn how to manage your service <a href="https://boost.com.au/hello"><u>here</u></a>.</p>
<p> </p>
<p>If your Boost SIM has not been activated within 24 hours, please <a href="https://boost.com.au/get-help/"><u>Message us</u></a></p>]]>
    </content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://boost.com.au/blogs/help-topics/how-to-set-up-auto-recharge</id>
    <published>2021-03-16T11:38:56+11:00</published>
    <updated>2023-11-15T14:55:48+11:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://boost.com.au/blogs/help-topics/how-to-set-up-auto-recharge"/>
    <title>How to Setup Boost Auto Recharge</title>
    <author>
      <name>John-Scott McClure</name>
    </author>
    <content type="html">
      <![CDATA[<h1>How do I set up Auto recharge?</h1>
<p>With auto recharge your phone will automatically recharge on expiry so you don't need to worry about recharging.</p>
<h3><strong><span data-mce-fragment="1">How to set up auto recharge using My Boost Mobile App:</span></strong></h3>
<p>Take the hassle out of recharging - follow these simple steps:</p>
<p class="m_3262901000646446680xmsonormal"><u>Payments Tab:</u></p>
<p class="m_3262901000646446680xmsonormal">To set up Auto Recharge:<br>1. Sign in to the My Boost App with your Username and Password<br>2. Go to the Payments tab and ‘Auto recharge’ under the Recharge section<br>3. Select the auto recharge amount and confirm</p>
<p class="m_3262901000646446680xmsonormal"><u>Services Tab:</u><span class="im"><br>1. Sign in to the My Boost App with your Username and Password<br></span>2. Go to the Services tab and select your Boost Pre-Paid service<br>3. Scroll down to ‘More with your Mobile’ section and select Auto Recharge<br>4. Select the auto recharge amount and confirm</p>
<h3>How to set up auto recharge using My Boost Mobile Online<br><br>
</h3>
<p>1. Go to the <a href="https://myaccount.boost.com.au/">website</a><br>2. Enter your Username and password and click the black "sign in" button.<br data-mce-fragment="1">3. Confirm your identity through the two-step verification. Select where you'd like us to send your one-time code. e.g. email or phone number. Then tap the black "Next" button.<br data-mce-fragment="1">4. Enter the 6 digit code then click the "Next" button.<br data-mce-fragment="1">5. Go to "Services" tab and the choose "Manage Pre-paid".<br data-mce-fragment="1">6. Scroll down to More with your mobile section and select "Auto recharge:Off"<br data-mce-fragment="1">7. Select your auto recharge amount and follow the prompts<br><br>If you're on one of our older plans (e.g. Anytime Ultra or Anytime Plus), you will be able to set up auto recharge in a couple of months<span>, once you’ve been moved onto our new plans and are eligible to use the new My Boost Mobile app. We will notify you when this has taken place.</span> </p>
<p>Still got questions on Auto Recharge? Check out our full Auto Recharge <a href="https://boost.com.au/auto-recharge/" style="font-size: 15px;" data-mce-style="font-size: 15px;">FAQs</a><span style="font-size: 15px;" data-mce-style="font-size: 15px;">.</span></p>]]>
    </content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://boost.com.au/blogs/help-topics/request-refund</id>
    <published>2021-03-16T11:33:59+11:00</published>
    <updated>2021-12-20T12:03:16+11:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://boost.com.au/blogs/help-topics/request-refund"/>
    <title>Request A Refund</title>
    <author>
      <name>John-Scott McClure</name>
    </author>
    <content type="html">
      <![CDATA[<h1>How do I request a refund?</h1>
<p><strong>If you made a purchase on the Boost website</strong></p>
<p>If you believe you’ve been incorrectly charged and would like a refund, please <a href="https://boost.com.au/get-help/"><u>Message us</u></a> (7am-11pm AEST, 7 days)</p>
<p><b>If you made a purchase in a retailer</b></p>
<p>Please return the product with receipt to the retailer you purchased it from.</p>]]>
    </content>
  </entry>
</feed>
