<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<feed xml:lang="en" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:opensearch="http://a9.com/-/spec/opensearch/1.1/" xmlns:s="http://jadedpixel.com/-/spec/shopify">
  <id>https://boost.com.au/blogs/help-topics.atom</id>
  <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://boost.com.au/blogs/help-topics"/>
  <link rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" href="https://boost.com.au/blogs/help-topics/tagged/other.atom"/>
  <title>Boost Mobile Australia - Help Topics</title>
  <updated>2024-02-14T06:46:40+11:00</updated>
  <author>
    <name>Boost Mobile Australia</name>
  </author>
  <entry>
    <id>https://boost.com.au/blogs/help-topics/where-to-go-for-help-support</id>
    <published>2021-12-03T17:19:11+11:00</published>
    <updated>2021-12-03T17:20:45+11:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://boost.com.au/blogs/help-topics/where-to-go-for-help-support"/>
    <title>Where to go for Help &amp; Support</title>
    <author>
      <name>Emily Peake</name>
    </author>
    <content type="html">
      <![CDATA[<h1>Where to go for Help &amp; Support</h1>
<p>If you have a question, chances are someone else has a similar one.</p>
<p>Check out our <a href="https://boost.com.au/pages/help-topics" title="Boost FAQs">FAQs</a> , <a href="https://refurbished.boost.com.au/pages/frequently-asked-questions" title="Refurbished FAQs">Refurbished FAQs</a>, or our <a href="https://boost.com.au/pages/get-help" title="Help &amp; Support Blog">Help &amp; Support articles.</a></p>
<p>Or you can get it touch using of the following methods:</p>
<ul>
<li>Chat to us on <a href="https://www.facebook.com/boostaus" target="_blank" title="Boost Mobile Australia Facebook" rel="noopener noreferrer">Facebook</a> - available 24/7</li>
<li>Message Us - available 7am-11pm AEST, 7 days</li>
<li>Call us on 1800 100 933 - available 8am-8pm AEST, 7days </li>
</ul>
<p> </p>]]>
    </content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://boost.com.au/blogs/help-topics/how-to-use-google-pay</id>
    <published>2021-12-03T17:04:47+11:00</published>
    <updated>2023-10-25T10:32:05+11:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://boost.com.au/blogs/help-topics/how-to-use-google-pay"/>
    <title>How to use Google Pay - Help and Support - Boost Mobile</title>
    <author>
      <name>Emily Peake</name>
    </author>
    <content type="html">
      <![CDATA[<h1>How to use Google Pay</h1>
<p>Google Pay is a mobile payments app that allows you to store your credit &amp; debit cards, shopping (aka loyalty) cards all in a simple and easy location on your supported Android phone.<br> <br><strong>So can I use Google Pay?</strong><br><strong> </strong><br>There are a few things to check to ensure you are ready for Google Pay</p>
<ul>
<li>Is your bank / financial provider supporting Google Pay? Check out the list of available providers <a href="https://support.google.com/pay/answer/7351634" target="_blank" title="Google Pay Providers" rel="noopener noreferrer">here</a>
</li>
<li>Make sure your phone is running at least Android Kit Kat 4.4 or higher</li>
<li>You need to download the Google Pay app to your Android device. You can find that<span> </span><a href="https://play.google.com/store/apps/details?id=com.google.android.apps.walletnfcrel" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer" title="Google Pay App">here</a>.</li>
<li>Make sure you have a compatible phone. Most flagship Android phones from the last two years can use Google Pay, however if you were not sure, open the Google Pay app and check its compatibility. If your device is not compatible you will receive one of the following error messages - "Google Pay can’t be used”, “Google is unable to verify your device”, “You can no longer use Google Pay on this phone”.</li>
</ul>
<p><strong>How do I set up Google Pay?</strong></p>
<p>Simply head over to the Google Pay app and click the blue ‘get started’ button! This will guide you through the process to add your specific card and even give you the option to scan your card using your device’s camera so you don’t need to type in those numbers! (You can also type your numbers in manually if this is your thing)</p>
<p>Once done, you will go through a security verification process (just to make sure it’s you) then voila, you’re done!<br> <br><strong>Is Google Pay safe?</strong></p>
<p>Google Pay has a multi-layered secured system to ensure your transactions are safe. When you are making a payment in store, Google Pay is not sharing the actual card information. The merchant is instead receiving a unique and encrypted number to complete the transaction.</p>
<p>Even if you lose your phone, you can use the ‘Find my phone’ feature and shut down access to Google Pay.<br> <br><strong>So where can I use Google Pay?</strong></p>
<p>Anywhere that has the Google Pay logo. This can often be found on the EFTPOS pad and / or register where you are making the purchase. Simply when prompted, hold your phone up to the EFTPOS pad and your phone will confirm payment has been made.</p>]]>
    </content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://boost.com.au/blogs/help-topics/how-to-use-apple-pay</id>
    <published>2021-12-03T16:58:55+11:00</published>
    <updated>2023-10-25T10:31:42+11:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://boost.com.au/blogs/help-topics/how-to-use-apple-pay"/>
    <title>How to use Apple Pay - Help and Support - Boost Mobile</title>
    <author>
      <name>Emily Peake</name>
    </author>
    <content type="html">
      <![CDATA[<h1>How to use Apple Pay?</h1>
<p>Apple pay is making it easier to make purchases from your iPhone or Apple Watch. Make everyday purchases in stores, in-apps and on participating websites in ways simpler and safer than using your actual card.<br><br><strong>So can I use Apple Pay?</strong></p>
<p>There are a few things to check to ensure you are ready for Apple Pay.</p>
<ul>
<li>Is your bank / financial provider supporting Apple Pay? Check out the list of available providers <a href="https://support.apple.com/en-au/HT206638" title="Apple Pay Providers">here</a>
</li>
<li>Is your Apple Device compatible? Apple Pay works on iPhone 6, 6 Plus, iPhone 6S, 6S Plus, 7, 7 Plus, 8, 8 Plus, iPhone X, iPhone SE, iPad Air 2, iPad Pro and the Apple Watch.</li>
<li>You have the latest version of iOS on your device. Simply head to Settings &gt; General &gt; Software Update</li>
</ul>
<p> </p>
<p><strong>How do I set up Apple Pay?</strong></p>
<p>Does your device meet the above? Great! Simply head to the ‘Wallet’ app on your device and select ‘Add Credit or Debit Card’ and follow the prompts. This will go through a process to ensure everything is compatible for use.<br><br><strong>Is Apple Pay Safe?</strong></p>
<p>Apple Pay utilises a number which is specific to your device and a transaction number that is unique to this type of transaction. Your card number is not stored on your device nor are they shared with merchants using Apple Pay. Plus, it’s always handy to have either a pin or Face ID enabled on your device for added protection.<br><br><strong>Where can I use Apple Pay?</strong></p>
<p>Simply look for the Apple Pay logo. Generally these can be found at the checkout or on the EFTPOS pad.</p>]]>
    </content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://boost.com.au/blogs/help-topics/boost-id</id>
    <published>2021-12-03T15:49:06+11:00</published>
    <updated>2023-11-16T11:14:39+11:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://boost.com.au/blogs/help-topics/boost-id"/>
    <title>Username and Password - Help and Support - Boost Mobile</title>
    <author>
      <name>Emily Peake</name>
    </author>
    <content type="html">
      <![CDATA[<h1><span data-mce-fragment="1">What is my username and password?</span></h1>
<p><strong><span data-mce-fragment="1">Formerly known as a Boost ID, your Boost username and password are used to access and manage your Boost service.</span></strong></p>
<p>Your username is the email address you used to activate your Boost service with us. It enables you to securely access and manage specific features in the app, such as:<br data-mce-fragment="1"><br>- Set up and manage auto recharge<br data-mce-fragment="1">- Save and manage your credit / debit card details<br data-mce-fragment="1">- Manage multiple services<br data-mce-fragment="1">- View your usage history<br data-mce-fragment="1">- View your recharge history</p>
<h3>How to recover username in the My Boost Mobile app:</h3>
<p>1. Open the My Boost Mobile app and tap the black "Sign in" button at the bottom of the screen.<br>2. Tap "Recover username" under the username text field.<br>3. Choose how you want to recover the username by selecting email address or Boost mobile number.<br>4. Tap the black "Let's get started" button. <br>5. Now enter your email address. <br>6. You should receive an email from us shortly with you username. If you can't find it in your inbox, please check your junk mail.<br>7. Tap the sign in button.</p>
<h3>How do I reset my password?</h3>
<p>When prompted, enter your username in the box provided, and click Send. <br data-mce-fragment="1"><br data-mce-fragment="1">An email will be sent with a link to reset your password. Simply click on the link and follow the prompts.<br data-mce-fragment="1"><br>Now you're good to go! You can sign into the My Boost Mobile app and access the additional features.<br data-mce-fragment="1"><br></p>
<ol></ol>]]>
    </content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://boost.com.au/blogs/help-topics/wifi-calling</id>
    <published>2021-12-03T15:30:48+11:00</published>
    <updated>2023-10-25T10:38:11+11:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://boost.com.au/blogs/help-topics/wifi-calling"/>
    <title>Wi-Fi Calling - Help and Support - Boost Mobile</title>
    <author>
      <name>Emily Peake</name>
    </author>
    <content type="html">
      <![CDATA[<h1>Does Boost support Wi-Fi Calling?</h1>
<p>Wi-Fi calling enables you to make calls using a fixed Wi-Fi connection from your compatible Boost phone when you can’t connect to the mobile network. Your phone simply uses your Wi-Fi network instead of the mobile network, so you can make and receive calls as you would normally.</p>
<p> </p>
<p><strong>To use Wi-Fi calling, you need to:</strong></p>
<ul>
<li>Have a Wi-Fi calling compatible smartphone or tablet</li>
<li>Have 4G voice calls enabled</li>
<li>Have up-to-date software</li>
<li>Turn on Wi-Fi calling</li>
</ul>
<p> </p>
<p><strong><span class="heading-16">How do I turn on Wi-Fi calling?</span></strong></p>
<p>For iPhone:</p>
<ol>
<li>Go to <strong>Settings</strong>
</li>
<li>Select <strong>Mobile</strong>
</li>
<li>Turn on <strong>Wi-Fi calling</strong>
</li>
</ol>
<p> </p>
<p>For Android devices:</p>
<ol>
<li>Go to your phone's calling app</li>
<li>Select <strong>More </strong>or the three dots in the top right corner</li>
<li>Select <strong>Settings</strong>
</li>
<li>Turn on <strong>Wi-Fi Calling</strong>
</li>
</ol>]]>
    </content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://boost.com.au/blogs/help-topics/included-calls</id>
    <published>2021-12-03T13:48:03+11:00</published>
    <updated>2023-10-25T10:33:08+11:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://boost.com.au/blogs/help-topics/included-calls"/>
    <title>Included Calls - Help and Support - Boost Mobile</title>
    <author>
      <name>Emily Peake</name>
    </author>
    <content type="html">
      <![CDATA[<h1>What types of calls are included in Boost plans?</h1>
<p>All our plans include unlimited calls and text to standard national numbers, which means you can call regular landline and mobile numbers as much as you like. This also includes most 1800, 1300 or 13 numbers.</p>
<p>It e<span>xcludes calls and texts to international numbers, satellite and premium numbers (eg. 19xx numbers), operator assisted calls (most 12xx numbers) and all use overseas.</span></p>
<p>Some of our plans also include standard calls to international numbers.</p>
<p>For more information about our current plan inclusions, click <a href="https://boost.com.au/pages/prepaid-plans" title="Prepaid Plans">here</a>.</p>]]>
    </content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://boost.com.au/blogs/help-topics/data-sharing</id>
    <published>2021-12-03T13:40:43+11:00</published>
    <updated>2023-10-25T10:30:22+11:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://boost.com.au/blogs/help-topics/data-sharing"/>
    <title>Data Sharing - Help and Support - Boost Mobile</title>
    <author>
      <name>Emily Peake</name>
    </author>
    <content type="html">
      <![CDATA[<h1>Does Boost offer data sharing?</h1>
<p>No, Boost doesn't offer data sharing between your service and and another Boost service.</p>]]>
    </content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://boost.com.au/blogs/help-topics/smart-watch</id>
    <published>2021-12-03T13:26:31+11:00</published>
    <updated>2023-10-25T10:37:02+11:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://boost.com.au/blogs/help-topics/smart-watch"/>
    <title>Smart watch compatibility - Help and Support - Boost Mobile</title>
    <author>
      <name>Emily Peake</name>
    </author>
    <content type="html">
      <![CDATA[<h1>Can I use my Smart watch with Boost?</h1>
<p>Boost doesn't currently support the use of cellular Smartwatches with your existing number, including Apple watches and Samsung Galaxy watches.</p>
<p><span>However we are working on it as we know its something our customers are interested in.</span></p>]]>
    </content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://boost.com.au/blogs/help-topics/does-boost-have-esim-capability</id>
    <published>2021-12-03T13:19:57+11:00</published>
    <updated>2024-03-12T14:43:25+11:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://boost.com.au/blogs/help-topics/does-boost-have-esim-capability"/>
    <title>Does Boost have eSIM capability</title>
    <author>
      <name>Emily Peake</name>
    </author>
    <content type="html">
      <![CDATA[<h1>Does Boost Mobile have eSIM capability?</h1>
<p>We sure do! And the best news... All of our plans are available on eSIM.</p>
<p>All you have to do to sign up for your eSIM service is download the My Boost Mobile app and select “Buy a prepaid plan on eSIM” and follow the prompts. It’s pretty straightforward though, tbh.</p>
<p><a href="https://boost.com.au/pages/esim" title="eSIM Boost Mobile">More info on Boost Mobile eSIM.</a></p>]]>
    </content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://boost.com.au/blogs/help-topics/change-account-ownership</id>
    <published>2021-12-01T15:35:06+11:00</published>
    <updated>2023-10-25T10:28:46+11:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://boost.com.au/blogs/help-topics/change-account-ownership"/>
    <title>Change account ownership - Help and Support - Boost Mobile</title>
    <author>
      <name>Emily Peake</name>
    </author>
    <content type="html">
      <![CDATA[<h1>How to change your account ownership</h1>
<p>To transfer your account to another person, or to update account details, please contact us. You can call 1800 100 933 or Message Us on our <a href="https://boost.com.au/pages/get-help" target="_blank" title="Help" rel="noopener noreferrer">help</a> page.</p>]]>
    </content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://boost.com.au/blogs/help-topics/extend-your-ring-time</id>
    <published>2021-12-01T15:04:34+11:00</published>
    <updated>2023-10-25T10:30:41+11:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://boost.com.au/blogs/help-topics/extend-your-ring-time"/>
    <title>Extend your ring time - Help and Support - Boost Mobile</title>
    <author>
      <name>Emily Peake</name>
    </author>
    <content type="html">
      <![CDATA[<h1>How to extend your ring time</h1>
<p>To extend your phone's ring time, follow these simple steps:</p>
<ol>
<li>On your Boost mobile dial **61*101**(number of seconds: 15, 20, 25 or 30)#</li>
<li>Press the Call/Send button</li>
</ol>
For example, to extend your ring time to 30 seconds, you would dial **61*101**30#]]>
    </content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://boost.com.au/blogs/help-topics/manage-your-service</id>
    <published>2021-12-01T12:32:15+11:00</published>
    <updated>2024-03-26T15:37:45+11:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://boost.com.au/blogs/help-topics/manage-your-service"/>
    <title>Manage your service - Help and Support - Boost Mobile</title>
    <author>
      <name>Emily Peake</name>
    </author>
    <content type="html">
      <![CDATA[<h1>How to manage your service</h1>
<p><strong>The easiest way to manage your service is in the My Boost Mobile app and online.</strong></p>
<p>With the My Boost Mobile app you can recharge, set up auto recharge, check you balance, see your usage &amp; recharge history, get help and more. </p>
<p>My Boost Mobile is available for <a href="https://apps.apple.com/au/app/my-boost-mobile/id1536871973" title="My Boost Mobile App iOS" target="_blank">iOS</a> and <a href="https://play.google.com/store/apps/details?id=com.boost.mobile.myboost" title="My Boost Mobile app Android" target="_blank">Android</a> and is for customers on the Boost Mobile Prepaid Plan. </p>
<p>You can also recharge on our website by <a href="https://myaccount.boost.com.au/" title="sign in">signing in</a> or using our online<a href="https://boost.com.au/enternumber" title="Quick recharge"> recharge</a> option. </p>
<p> </p>]]>
    </content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://boost.com.au/blogs/help-topics/prank-or-unwanted-calls</id>
    <published>2021-12-01T12:24:03+11:00</published>
    <updated>2023-10-25T10:35:40+11:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://boost.com.au/blogs/help-topics/prank-or-unwanted-calls"/>
    <title>Spam, prank or unwanted calls - Help and Support - Boost Mobile</title>
    <author>
      <name>Emily Peake</name>
    </author>
    <content type="html">
      <![CDATA[<h1>How to stop spam, prank or unwanted calls</h1>
<p>If you are experiencing nuisance calls or messages, please contact us so we can further investigate it with you. You can either call us on 1800 100 933 or Message us by clicking "Message Us" on our <a href="https://boost.com.au/pages/get-help" target="_blank" title="Help" rel="noopener noreferrer">Help</a> page </p>
<p>If you are getting telemarking calls you can sign up for the <a href="https://www.donotcall.gov.au" target="_blank" title="Do Not Call Register" rel="noopener noreferrer">Do Not Call</a> register. You can also report unwanted calls to the Australian Communications &amp; Media Authority <a href="https://www.acma.gov.au/" target="_blank" title="ACMA" rel="noopener noreferrer">here</a>.</p>]]>
    </content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://boost.com.au/blogs/help-topics/sim-card-error</id>
    <published>2021-12-01T10:57:16+11:00</published>
    <updated>2023-10-25T10:36:38+11:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://boost.com.au/blogs/help-topics/sim-card-error"/>
    <title>SIM Card Error - Help and Support - Boost Mobile</title>
    <author>
      <name>Emily Peake</name>
    </author>
    <content type="html">
      <![CDATA[<h1>How can I fix my SIM card error?</h1>
<p><strong>There are a number of reasons that you are experiencing a SIM card error.</strong></p>
<p><strong></strong>If your SIM is not installed properly, try turning off the phone, taking the sim out and putting it back in (make sure it it seated correctly) before restarting your phone. </p>
<p>If this doesn't work, your SIM may be damaged or faulty and you'll likely need to order a replacement SIM.</p>
<p>Please contact us to further troubleshoot your error or order a replacement SIM. You can either give us a call on 125 88881 ( 8am-8pm AEST 7 days) or Message us <a href="https://boost.com.au/pages/get-help" target="_blank" title="Help" rel="noopener noreferrer">here</a>.</p>]]>
    </content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://boost.com.au/blogs/help-topics/check-for-service-disruptions</id>
    <published>2021-12-01T10:48:05+11:00</published>
    <updated>2023-10-25T10:29:32+11:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://boost.com.au/blogs/help-topics/check-for-service-disruptions"/>
    <title>Check for service disruptions - Help and Support - Boost Mobile</title>
    <author>
      <name>Emily Peake</name>
    </author>
    <content type="html">
      <![CDATA[<h1 style="text-align: left;">How to check for outages or service disruptions</h1>
<p style="text-align: left;"><span></span><span><strong>If you are unable to use your Boost Mobile to send SMS, make calls or get online, it may be due to a disruption to Boost Mobile services. These issues can range from hardware faults to outages or scheduled maintenance on the Telstra Mobile Network infrastructure.</strong></span></p>
<p style="text-align: left;">Click <a title="Service Status Tool" href="https://outages.telstra.com.au/#/mobile?pageSource=home" target="_blank">here</a> to check if there is an outage or service disruption in your area. </p>
<p style="text-align: left;">On this page you'll find updates on issues affecting our services across the country and where possible, provide an estimate restoration time so you know how long it will be until services are back up and running. </p>
<p style="text-align: left;">If there are no known issues in your area, please contact us. The easiest way to get in touch is to Message us from our <a title="Help" href="https://boost.com.au/pages/get-help">Help</a> page. </p>]]>
    </content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://boost.com.au/blogs/help-topics/get-your-pin-or-puk-code</id>
    <published>2021-03-16T11:28:35+11:00</published>
    <updated>2023-09-27T17:25:45+10:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://boost.com.au/blogs/help-topics/get-your-pin-or-puk-code"/>
    <title>How To Get Your PUK or PIN code?</title>
    <author>
      <name>John-Scott McClure</name>
    </author>
    <content type="html">
      <![CDATA[<h1>How do I get my PIN or PUK code?</h1>
<p><strong>On your SIM packaging</strong></p>
<p>When you buy your SIM card, it’s attached to a larger piece of plastic that you pop it out of. Your actual SIM also has a series of numbers printed on it. Your PUK code is the 8 digit number found on either the SIM or the additional SIM packaging.</p>
<p>By default, your PIN code is the last 4 digits of your PUK code – but obviously if you’ve changed your PIN code yourself, this will no longer apply.</p>
<p><strong>Or speak to the customer service team</strong></p>
<p>You can call our team on 1800 100 933 (8am-8pm, AEST 7 days) or <a href="https://boost.com.au/pages/get-help"><u>Message us </u></a>(7am-11pm, AEST 7 days) and one of the team will be able to help get the info you need.</p>]]>
    </content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://boost.com.au/blogs/help-topics/cancel-your-service</id>
    <published>2021-03-16T11:27:32+11:00</published>
    <updated>2021-12-20T11:58:46+11:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://boost.com.au/blogs/help-topics/cancel-your-service"/>
    <title>Cancel Your Service</title>
    <author>
      <name>John-Scott McClure</name>
    </author>
    <content type="html">
      <![CDATA[<h1>Cancel your service</h1>
<p><strong>If your phone isn’t recharged for a period of 6 months</strong><span> it will be deemed inactive and you will lose your number.</span></p>
<p><span>To cancel your service please <a href="https://boost.com.au/get-help/"><u>message us</u></a> (7am-11pm AEST, 7 days).</span></p>]]>
    </content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://boost.com.au/blogs/help-topics/replacement-sim</id>
    <published>2021-03-16T11:13:09+11:00</published>
    <updated>2023-07-07T10:12:58+10:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://boost.com.au/blogs/help-topics/replacement-sim"/>
    <title>Boost Mobile Replacement SIM</title>
    <author>
      <name>John-Scott McClure</name>
    </author>
    <content type="html">
      <![CDATA[<meta charset="utf-8">
<h1>How do I get a replacement SIM?</h1>
<p>If you’ve lost your SIM or got a new phone and your SIM card doesn’t fit, don’t worry. We can organise a new SIM to be sent out to you ASAP.</p>
<p><strong>All you need to do is call us on one of the numbers below and we’ll then send it out to you.</strong></p>
<p><strong></strong><strong>Boost Services: 125 8881 </strong>(When calling from a Boost/Telstra service)<strong><br>New Customers: 1800 100 933 </strong>(When calling from a non-Boost/Telstra service)<strong><br></strong></p>
<p>We’ll also give you the option to suspend your service until the new SIM is received – just in case someone tries to use it. When you replace your SIM, you won’t lose your credit but credit expiry periods will still be applicable. If your credit is about to expire, you can  to retain the credit balance until you receive your replacement SIM card.</p>
<p>You also won’t lose your mobile number when you get your replacement SIM card.</p>]]>
    </content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://boost.com.au/blogs/help-topics/sim-card-size</id>
    <published>2021-03-16T11:11:30+11:00</published>
    <updated>2021-12-20T12:19:35+11:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://boost.com.au/blogs/help-topics/sim-card-size"/>
    <title>SIM Card Size: What Do You Need?</title>
    <author>
      <name>John-Scott McClure</name>
    </author>
    <content type="html">
      <![CDATA[<meta charset="utf-8">
<h1>What SIM card size do I need?</h1>
<p><strong>There are three different SIM card sizes for phones: Standard, Micro and Nano.</strong></p>
<p>The best way to find out the size of your SIM is on the packaging your phone came in or the website for your phone type. Here are some general tips that might help you:</p>
<p><strong>Standard SIM</strong> – will fit most feature phones</p>
<p><strong>Micro SIM</strong> – will fit most Android or Windows phones (including iPhone 4/4S, Samsung Galaxy S4 and Samsung Galaxy S5)</p>
<p><strong>Nano SIM</strong> – will fit most iPhones (eg. iPhone 5 and iPhone 6 Plus)</p>
<p><strong>All Boost SIM packs contain Trio SIMs</strong></p>
<p>﻿Trio SIMs can be used for all SIM card sizes - simply pop out the SIM size you need.</p>]]>
    </content>
  </entry>
</feed>
